Guide to the Spanish Civil War Poster Collection ALBA.GRAPHICS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Spanish Civil War Posters from the Tamiment Library Poster Collection, 1936-1938.
  - Goñi (SDP). "Organitzeu Festivales Esportiu: A Profit de les Milicies. Comissariat de Propaganda (Seccio Festivals Benefics). Comite Catala Pro Esport Popular." [Published by] UHP, Sindicat de Dibuixants Professionals, UGT. Imprint "Ultra S.A. Corcega 220-Barcelona." H: 39 3/8 x W: 27 1/4 inches., 1937 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_f13c3bd7153e4c65f2e2698a68be5ec7, Item TAM-ES 50.0-14)
  - Gumsay (Saomz Moral). "Eliseo Reclus: La Anarquia es La Mas Alta Expresion del Orden." [Published by] J.J. L.L. De Cataluna. Imprint "Relieves-Basa & Pages, Colectivizada-Barcelona." H: 35 1/2 x W: 25 3/4 inches., 1937 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_32f238d32b1c54d48594ab2b1c2e3f2b, Item TAM-ES 50.0-12)
  - Herreros. "Imitad: Al Heroe del Pueblo." H: 53 1/4 x W: 39 3/8 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_9dc65c793a63376c454695ed27d74aa5, Item TAM-ES 50.0-7 [0])
  - Lau (Nicolau Miralles Garcia). "Regions i comarques …: Generalitat de Catalunya, Conselleria d’Economia Conselleria d'Econmia, Octubre 1936." [Published by] POUM. Imprint "Seix i Barral, Empresa Collectivitzada-Barcelona." H: 49 x W: 35 1/4 inches. (Duplicate of ALBA-ES 64). (Drawer East Wing Aisles 21-22 (top), Folder data_value_missing_53eec05fbf2699d96c3cb6654c260715, Item TAM-ES 50.0-3 [0])
  - Lienas. "El Socialismo es La Liberacion." [Published by] POUM. Imprint "Atl'antida, AGP de la Republica 34-T52636, Barna." H: 53 1/4 x W: 39 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer East Wing Aisles 21-22 (top), Folder data_value_missing_1d844d412114b6f7dd57e70da6a0f77c, Item TAM-ES 50.0-8 [0])
  - Milla. "Escola Nova: Poble Lliure." [Published by] CENU. Imprint "I.G. Seix y Barral, Germs. SA-Barcelona." H: 39 x W: 27 3/8 inches., 1936 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_a4712cdc906ba467b5060df01e8d12de, Item TAM-ES 50.0-6)
  - Muro (fotomontage.) "Kultur! La Barbarie Fasciste a Madrid." [Published by] CNT/AIT: Comite Nacional -Seccion Propaganda. Imprint "S. Dura, Valencia." H: 39 1/2 x W: 26 7/8 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM ES 50.0-21]., 1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_303350b8b5ebc1fa3ae9e6dab0154aab, Item TAM-ES 50.0-20)
  - Muro (fotomontage.) "Kultur! La Barbarie Fasciste a Madrid." [Published by] CNT/AIT: Comite Nacional -Seccion Propaganda. Imprint "S. Dura, Valencia." H: 39 1/2 x W: 26 7/8 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM ES 50.0-20]., 1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_edcd21ecf4578037c315f06329208af9, Item TAM-ES 50.0-21)
  - Prives, S. H. "Ajudeu als Herois Bascs!" [Published by] Comitè d’Ajut a Euscadi, Secretaria Basc, T. 15979. Imprint "Juan, viladomat.55-Barcelona, ca. maig de 1937." H: 35 1/2 x W: 25 1/2 inches. (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_61ad010c281b98dab551db30107aa2ed, Item TAM-ES 50.0-4)
  - R. A. "Socorro Rojo: Ayudadlo!" [Published by] POUM Imprint "Atl'antida, A.G. Roger de Flor 5-T-52636, Barna." H: 39 1/4 x W: 27 1/2 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_9ff7b4d4eeb5c8fc6ba0e793c15b4b3d, Item TAM-ES 50.0-5)
  - Swie. "Campesinos: La Tierra es Vuestra." [Published by] POUM. Imprint "Atl'antida, AGP dela Republica 34-T52636, Barna." H: 39 1/2 x W: 27 3/4 inches., 1936 (Drawer East Wing Aisles 21-22 (top), Folder data_value_missing_1496e9e16c197f3acc72a13e953fc589, Item TAM-ES 50.0-11)
  - Swie. "Periodico de la Juventud: Juvento Comunista." [Published by] UGT-CNT. Imprint "Comite Obrero del Control Ortega, Dalencia." H: 39 3/8 x W: 26 3/4 inches., 1936 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_442384bfa541719c07582f57e3d7223c, Item TAM-ES 50.0-9)
  - Siwe. "Trabajadores: El POUM os Espera." [Published by] POUM. Imprint "Atl'antida, AGP de la Republica 34-T52636, Barna." H: 39 3/8 x W: 27 1/2 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM-ES 50.0-8]., 1936 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_e0c081d713dd8ac15a40decff4e0e7dd, Item TAM-ES 50.0-7)
  - Siwe. "Trabajadores: El POUM os Espera." [Published by] POUM Imprint "Atl'antida, AGP de la Republica 34-T52636, Barna." H: 39 3/8 x W: 27 1/2 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM-ES 50.0-7]., 1936 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_647302718d4f5280eb34aaab5674a81a, Item TAM-ES 50.0-8)
  - Vicente, E. "Trabajadores!!: Leed - Solidaridad Obrera - Diario de La Revolucion." [Published by] Dibujantes- CNT. H: 54 x W: 39 1/4 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_93361f02a22669e39e1fea20ea4de66a, Item TAM-ES 50.0-10 [0])
  - Vilato, Badia. "Ambiciones, Militarismo, Guerra. Esto Es El Fascismo. Destruyelo Uniendo Tu Esfuerzo Al De Los Demas." [Published by] CNT/FAI. Imprint "Indústries Gràfiques Seix i Barral, E.C. -Barcelona." H: 42 3/4 x W: 29 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM-ES 50.0-5 [0]]., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_139d89050676afaa4e6105f0eaf7a093, Item TAM-ES 50.0-4 [0])
  - Vilato, Badia. "Ambiciones, Militarismo, Guerra. Esto Es El Fascismo. Destruyelo Uniendo Tu Esfuerzo Al De Los Demas." [Published by] CNT/FAI. Imprint "Indústries Gràfiques Seix i Barral, E.C.-Barcelona." H: 42 3/4 x W: 29 inches. [Duplicate of: TAM-ES 50.0-4 [0]]., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_01c03ad08c6b9bea15cfbd415876bd29, Item TAM-ES 50.0-5 [0])
  - "Camperols Escolteu: Les Emissions Radiades de la Consellaria d'Agriculttura: Cada Dimarts I Divendres Ales 7i1/2 del Vespre." [Published by] UGT., Sindicat de Dibuixants Professionals. Imprint "Ultra S.A. Corcega 220-Barcelona." H: 39 1/4 x W: 27 3/8 inches. [Duplicate of: ALBA-ES 22]., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_d9ea3f86be618812b4031a603073aa7c, Item TAM-ES 50.0-13)
  - "Companys Camperols: Tots a Sembrar Ajudeu els vostres Germans del Front! Lliureu la Batalla de la Sembra. Editat Comissaria de Propaganda de la Generalitat de Catalunya - no.8.[fotomontage.] " [Published by] OOR.MA. H. 39 1/2 x W. 27 5/8 inches. [Duplicate of: ALBA ES 1]., 1937 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_210cedb826a3559b0a3507e30bf83996, Item TAM-ES 50.0-22)
  - "Estampas de la Espana que Sufre y Lucha. Album Editado por El Comite Regional de Juventudes Libertarias de Cataluna de Venta Aqui. Para paquteros revendeores en la casa CNT-FAI at Via Durruti 32-3 Piso. [with embedded Gumsay illustration]" [Published by] CNT/FAI. H: 16 7/8 x W: 11 1/2 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_b3453a04530e0e6077306268035b2c7d, Item TAM-ES 50.0-2)
  - "Juventudes!: El Mundo que se Aproxima Sera Conforme a Nuestra Manerade. Serv y Pensar." [Published by] J.J. L.L. of Catalan. Imprint "I.G. Seix y Barral - E.C.-Barcelona." H: 39 x W: 26 3/4 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer East Wing Aisles 21-22 (top), Folder data_value_missing_5f5121b20c0432fef2c819fdbd66d6ea, Item TAM-ES 50.0-10)
  - "Kion Vi Faras Por Evitition: Geesperantistoj el la Tuta Mondo Agu Energie Kontrau la Internacia Fasismo!" [Published by] Eldonita de Comissariat de Propaganda de la Generalitat de Catalunya. Imprint "Ultra S.A. Corcega 220-Barcelona." H: 39 1/2 x W: 27 5/8 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_ccf3a38298d376c63ec5944e6f5aed74, Item TAM-ES 50.0-17)
  - "L’Hora: Setmanari Portantveu del POUM Reapareix pel Triomf del Socialisme, Treballadors: Llegiu-Lo." H: 26 3/4 x W: 20 1/2 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_013d01c1e08605ecdaa84d7477f3fccd, Item TAM-ES 50.0-3)
  - "Mapa de Asia y Europa: Con Classificacion Social y Politica de las Naciones." H: 30 1/2 x W: 43 1/2 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_3ce82373ac03bc7c86190e9c4eee0e77, Item TAM-ES 50.0-1 [0])
  - [Quadruple profile of man with four types of tools.] Imprint "Atl'antida, AGP de la Republica 34-T52636, Barna." H: 39 1/2 x W: 27 5/8 inches., circa 1936-1938 (Drawer FFC: 6, 7, Folder data_value_missing_67b8b0b9df3540e29e9e1503d4401843, Item TAM-ES 50.0-18)